let allQuestions = [{
    question: "In the hit movie 'Die Hard', what is John MClane's famous catch-phrase?",
    a: 'Ho-Ho-Ho, now i have a machinegun!',
    b: 'Yippee-ki-yay!',
    c: 'Shoot the glass!',
    d: 'Easy now, cowboy!',
    answer: 'ans2'
}, {
    question: "How many prime directives did 'Robocop' have in the first original movie?",
    a: '4',
    b: '6',
    c: '3',
    d: '10',
    answer: 'ans1'
}, {
    question: "In 'Predator 2', after killing the City Hunter, Lieutenant Mike Harrigan receives a flintlock pistol. What year was engraved on it?",
    a: '1840',
    b: '1675',
    c: '1910',
    d: '1715',
    answer: 'ans4'
}, {
    question: "In the first 'Termiantor' movie, the T-800, played by Arnold Schwarzenegger, had what mission?",
    a: 'Protect John Connor',
    b: 'Eliminate Sarah Connor',
    c: 'Protect SkyNet',
    d: 'Eliminate mankind',
    answer: 'ans2'
}, {
    question: "In 'Star Wars: Revenge of the Sith', the fighting scene between Anakin Skywalker and Obi Wan Kenobi, who had higher ground?",
    a: 'Anakin Skywalker',
    b: 'Obi Wan Kenobi',
    c: 'Both',
    d: 'Neither',
    answer: 'ans2'
}, {
    question: "What was the name of the first film in the 'Harry Potter' series?",
    a: 'Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix',
    b: 'Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban',
    c: 'Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire',
    d: "Harry Potter And The Philosopher's Stone",
    answer: 'ans4'
}, {
    question: "In 'Beverly Hills Cop', Axel Foley was a cop from what city",
    a: 'Chicago',
    b: 'Beverly Hills',
    c: 'Detroit',
    d: 'New York',
    answer: 'ans3'
}, {
    question: "In what year was 'Rush Hour' produced?",
    a: '1998',
    b: '1999',
    c: '2000',
    d: '2001',
    answer: 'ans1'
}, {
    question: "Leonardo DiCaprio won his first Oscar for which movie?",
    a: 'The Wolf Of Wall Street',
    b: 'Django Unchained',
    c: 'The Revenant',
    d: 'Titanic',
    answer: 'ans3'
}, {
    question: "In 'Back To The Future', how many miles per hour did the DeLorean had to reach in order to time-travel?",
    a: '100',
    b: '88',
    c: '75',
    d: '90',
    answer: 'ans2'
}, ];